<resources>
    System.getProperty("line.separator")
    <string name="app_name">BookMySikkimShow</string>
    <string name="title_home">Events</string>
    <string name="rupees">₹</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">My Tickets</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Profile</string>
    <string name="covid">Covid Safety Guidelines</string>
    <string name="help_support">Help &amp; Support</string>
    <string name="term_condition">Term &amp; Conditution</string>
    <string name="dateDay">DAY &amp; DATE</string>
    <string name="coffee">Coffee &amp; Snakes</string>
    <string name="unlock">Unlock extra features &amp; great benefits</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>

    <string name="demo_places">The Amazon is critical to our efforts to avoid a climate catastrophe.
        Water vapor released from the Amazon creates vast “flying rivers” in the atmosphere, which

        influence rainfall and thus agricultural production in central and southern South America.
        And the billions of tons of carbon stored in the Amazon rain forest is of global importance
        to slowing climate change.</string>


    <string name="priseRange">PRICE RANGE</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="note">Taxes and extra charges will be applicable at the time of checkout</string>
    <string name="userName">hen you don’t have the time to write a personal message to every customer,
        a review request text template is an efficient way to give your happy customers a voice.</string>

    <string name="feedback_text">When you don’t have the time to write a personal message to every
        customer, a review request text template is an efficient way to give your happy customers a
        voice.

Besides, text
        messages have a 98% open rate and a 45% response rate. No other form of outreach comes close to these numbers.

So if you’re not using textmessages to generate<br><br></br> Google reviews, you’re leaving a lot of
            valuable social proof potential on the table. Google reviews are probably the most important type of reviews that you can earn for your business.

Where do business owners struggle? </br>Brainstorming how to ask for the review in the text. There’s a valid fear of not knowing what to say. At the very least, you could simply say, “Review us on Google.” </string>
    <string name="about_the_place"><u>About the Place</u></string>
    <string name="best_time_to_visit"><u>Best Time To Visit</u></string>
    <string name="gallery"><u>Gallery</u></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_my_staff_list">MyStaffList</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>

</resources>